커피 더 달래야겠어
우리 아기인형은?
I'll get coffee.
Want anything, baby doll?
됐어, 괜찮아
I'm fine. Thanks.
아무래도 '아기인형'을
따라잡을 순 없겠지?
I can't pull off "baby doll," can l?
그럼, '사탕입술' 사건 때
이미 포기했잖아
No, I think we learned that
from the "sugar lips" incident.
I'll make some tea.
- 차 가져올게
- 그래
뭐하니, 깜찍아?
How you doing, pumpkin?
됐다
-So it's going well for you two?
-I know. Really well.
- 두 사람 정말 잘돼 가네요
- 네, 그래서 말인데...
I'm gonna ask Phoebe
to move in with me.
함께 살까 생각 중이에요
- 세상에!
- 괜찮겠어요?
What do you think?
It's great!
When will you ask her?
너무 잘됐네요
언제 말할 거예요?
오늘밤에요
미리 말하지 마세요
Tonight. But don't say anything.
네, 약속할게요
I swear. I promise.
I'm so excited!
굉장한 소식이네요
But listen, do not
get her flowers, okay?
그런데 꽃다발은
절대 주지 말아요
Because she cries when they die.
Then there's the whole funeral.
시들면 펑펑 울면서
장례 치른다고 난리쳐요
-I'll see you after work, sweetie.
-Okay. Bye.
- 일 끝나고 봐
- 그래, 안녕
So, what movie should we see?
어때, 무슨 영화 볼까?
Gary's gonna ask you
to move in with him!
개리가 너랑 동거할 거래
What? Really?
뭐? 정말?
He made me promise not to tell,
but I couldn't hold it in any longer!
방금 카운터에서 그랬어
얘기하지 말랬지만
더는 못 참겠는걸
I can't believe this.
말도 안 돼
그래, 너무 빨라
빠르다니까, 빨라
Right? Because it's fast.
Because it's so fast. It's fast.
Relax. It's Phoebe, not you.
흥분하지 마
네가 아니라 피비야
Good for you, Phoebe.
Way to go.
축하한다, 잘 해봐
No, but it is fast, isn't it?
빠른 건 사실이잖아?
-I like him, but I'm not ready.
-So, what are you gonna do?
개리가 좋긴 하지만
난 아직 준비가 안 됐어
그럼 어쩔 건데?
I don't know. I'll just handle it.
I'll ask you to talk to him!
글쎄, 어떡하나
네가 얘기해봐라
Me? Why me?
내가? 왜 나지?
넌 책임지는 거 겁나잖아
Because you are
so afraid of commitment.
You talk to him. Make him scared
like you, make him a man.
너처럼 부담 느끼게 만들어
남자를 만들라고
I'll try, but I'm not sure
what good it'd do.
시도는 해보겠는데 장담은 못해
이젠 전처럼 두렵지가 않거든
I'm less afraid of commitment
than I used to be.
That is so sweet.
내 사랑
Still terrified.
I'll take care of it.
아직도 무서워
내가 처리할게
The One With the Ball
로스, 스태튼 아일랜드가
진짜 섬이냐?
Hey, Ross, is Staten lsland
really an island?
그러니까 스태튼 '아일랜드'지
That's why they call it
Staten "lsland."
Oh, I thought it was
like Long lsland.
롱아일랜드 같은 게 아니구나
그것도 섬이야
Also an island.
-What time is it?
-2:17.
- 몇 시나 됐어?
- 2시 17분
우리 이 공 한 시간이나
안 떨어뜨린 거 알아?
We haven't dropped
this ball for an hour.
정말이야?
Are you serious?
30분전부터 알았는데
일부러 말 안 했어
I realized it a half-hour ago,
but I didn't say anything.
I didn't wanna jinx it.
재수 없을까 봐
We are pretty good at this.
- 우리 실력도 괜찮은데
- 그럼
이런, 점심 먹는 것도 잊었다
We totally forgot about lunch.
That's the first time
I've ever missed a meal.
끼니 거른 건 생전 처음인걸
I think my pants are a little loose.
맞아, 바지가 헐렁해졌어
Hey, you guys. Is Monica here?
- 얘들아
- 어서 와
- 모니카 있어?
- 아니
내가 뭘 하나 샀는데
걔가 좋아할지 모르겠어
I bought something.
I'm not sure she'll like it.
좀 이상하게 보이겠지만
어렸을 때부터 갖고 싶던 거야
It may seem crazy, but I've wanted
this since I was a little girl.
숀 캐시디 판 샀구나
You bought Shaun Cassidy!
No. I wish!
아냐, 사고는 싶지
좋아, 준비됐어?
Okay, you ready?
- 그래
- 알았어
암고양이란다
Check it out.
What is it?
- 맙소사, 이게...
- 그 흉물단지는 뭐야?
What the hell is that?
It's a cat.
- 고양이잖아
- 그건 고양이가 아냐
That is not a cat!
Yes, it is!
맞다니까
Why is it inside out?
근데 왜 껍질이 뒤집혔어?
Excuse me!
미안하지만 얘는 최상급
순종 스핑크스 고양이야
But this is a purebred,
show-quality sphinx cat.
How much did you pay for that?
얼마 줬는데?
좀 비싸긴 하지만
흥정이 잘됐어
It was extravagant,
but I got a good deal.
- 그래? 얼마야
- 천 달러
-How much?
-Thousand bucks.
On a cat?
고양이 한 마리에?
고양이 아니라니까
It's not a cat!
For a thousand dollars,
you'd think at least it'd come with hair.
천 달러짜리면
최소한 털은 있어야지
밑에 뭐가 달렸든지
Or something.
All right. Listen, ball boys.
잘 들어, 볼보이들
My grandma had one when I was little.
It was the sweetest thing.
옛날에 할머니가 이런 녀석을
키웠는데 얼마나 귀여운지
It would sit in my lap
and just purr all day long.
종일 내 무릎에 앉아
가르랑거리곤 했어
I would drag a string
and it would chase it.
신발 끈을 땅에 끌면
막 쫓아다닌다
Free cats do that too, you know.
공짜 고양이도 그런 거 잘해
It's not a cat!
고양이 아냐
I'm really excited about this, okay?
I don't care what you think.
난 좋기만 하니까
너희 맘대로 생각해
I'm gonna set up a litter box
for Mrs. Whiskerson.
'수염 여사' 화장실이나
만들어줘야겠다
그럼 '복슬이'라고 하리?
What am I gonna call her?
Fluffy?
뭐 좀 먹을까?
아니면 공놀이나 계속할까?
Do you wanna get something to eat,
or see how long we can throw this ball?
The ball thing.
- 공 쪽으로 가자
- 그래?
Wouldn't it be great if we could go
for two hours without dropping it?
야, 두 시간 기록은 어때?
바닥에 안 떨어뜨리고
그거 좋지
Yeah, it would!
Let's do it.
- 해보자
- 좋아
왜?
I have to pee.
쉬 마려워
레이첼이 들어갔잖아
And Rachel's in the bathroom!
Man, I didn't think we'd make it.
뜻이 있는 곳에 길이 있나니
I know.
당연하지
손이나 바꾸지 마
Don't switch hands, okay?
아가씨들, 왜 잡혀왔수?
Hey, ladies.
What are you in here for?
What are you doing here?
챈들러, 여긴 웬일이죠?
- 범죄를 신고하려고
- 그래요?
I am here to report a crime.
우리가 떨어져 있는 게
범죄 아니겠어요?
It's a crime that
we don't spend time together.
What's up?
무슨 일이죠?
피비와 동거할 생각이라던데
그 얘기를 좀 해볼까하고
You're thinking about moving in with
Phoebe, and I thought we should talk.
You know, man to...
남자 대... 나로서
...well, me.
Sure, okay.
- 그러죠 뭐
- 좋아요
Are you crazy?
미친 건 아니죠?
Are you insane?
제정신이에요?
무릇 동거라 함은 두 남녀가
함께 사는 행위를 일컫는데
If you live with Phoebe, you two
are gonna be living together.
I considered that.
It'd make me happy.
그걸 왜 모르겠어요
행복할 것 같아요
-You mean scared.
-No, I mean happy.
- 겁나는 게 아니고?
- 아뇨, 행복이죠
Scared happy.
겁나는 행복?
What are you doing?
- 챈들러, 왜 이래요?
- 정신 차리라는 거지
I'm trying to open your eyes!
모르겠어요? 함께 살면
피비가 늘 옆에 있어요
If you live with Phoebe,
she is always gonna be there.
집에 가도 피비
잠자리에 들어도 피비
You get home, she's there.
You go to bed, she's there.
눈을 뜨면? 어김없이 피비
You wake up and, oh, yes, she's there.
난 그 순간이 기다려져요
I know. I can't wait!
Were your parents happy or something?
부모님이 뭐 좀
행복하셨나 보네?
사랑하는 사람을 찾은 건
큰 행운이라고 생각해요
I was lucky enough to find
someone that I really love.
I just want to be around her
as much as I can.
그 사람 곁에 있고
싶은 게 당연하죠
들어보니 괜찮은 것도 같네요
When you say it,
it doesn't sound so scary.
- 이제 알겠어요?
- 네, 그래요
You know what I'm saying?
Yeah, I think I do.
You know what?
이럴 게 아니라 같이 살아요
Move in with her. Move in right now.
Maybe I'll move in with Monica.
당장 같이 사는 거야
난 모니카랑 합치고
거긴 너무 일러요
No, it's too soon for you guys.
You're right about that.
그건 옳은 말이네
중생대 마스토돈의
화석이 발굴됐는데
When they found the remains
of the Mesozoic mastodon...
...they discovered what appeared
to be the remains...
입 속에서 고생대 양서류로
보이는 화석이 나온 거야
...of a Paleozoic amphibian in its jaws.
그게 어떻게 거기 들어갔을까?
How did it get there?
조용히 게임이나 하자
Maybe this should be more
of a quiet game.
Hey, guys.
- 안녕
- 어서 와
조이, 어제 내 시계를
여기 뒀는데
I left my watch here last night.
- 혹시 못 봤어?
- 모르겠는데
-lt was here. Where is it?
-I don't know.
I'm late for work.
빨리, 지각하겠어
How do you know?
You don't have a watch.
어떻게 알아?
시계도 없으면서
Can you stop throwing the ball
for one minute and help me find it?
두 사람 공놀이 잠깐 멈추고
내 시계 좀 찾아주면 안 돼?
글쎄, 안 되겠다
Oh, I don't know....
Yeah, can't do it.
- 왜?
- 제발 공만 떨어뜨리지 마
-What?
-Do not drop that ball.
- 그 공 안 떨어뜨린 게...
- 두 시간 27분이야
We haven't dropped it in....
Two hours, 27 minutes.
그래?
Really?
I won't make it in to work today.
오늘 못 나갈 거 같아요
몸이 안 좋아서...
I don't feel very good.
그렇지!
For a second, I thought I was
feeling better, but I'm not.
잠깐 괜찮은 것 같더니
역시 아니네요
그럼
Hey, Rach.
- 어서 와, 레이첼
- 안녕
놀라지 마시라
세 시간째 공 안 떨어뜨렸다
Check it out. Almost three hours
without dropping it.
Congratulations.
That's quite a waste of time.
그거 축하할 일이네
허송세월 잘들 한다
- 레이첼
- 응?
You have scratches all over you.
그 상처는 다 뭐야?
Well, it's my cat.
- 내 고양이
- 뭐?
-Oh, I got a cat.
-I don't want a cat!
- 고양이 샀어
- 난 고양이 싫어
- 걱정 마, 고양이 아냐
- 그럼
Don't worry, it's not a cat.
할머니 고양이랑은
너무 딴판이다
You guys, this cat is nothing
like my grandmother's cat.
순하지도 않고
귀엽지도 않고
It's not sweet.
It's not cute.
신발 끈을 바닥에다 끌어도
나만 쥐어뜯고 발광을 하잖아
I dragged a string, and it flipped out
and scratched the hell out of me.
I know this sounds crazy,
but every time this cat hisses at me...
너희는 웃을지도 모르지만
입 벌리고 뭐라는 줄 아니?
이러는 거야, '레이첼'
...I know it's saying, "Rachel!"
Doesn't sound as crazy
as paying $1000 for a cat.
천 달러짜리 고양이라 그런지
별로 안 웃기는걸
You paid $1000 for a cat
when you owe me $300?
내 돈 3백 달러는 안 갚으면서
고양이를 천 달러에 사?
Well, I was gonna let you
play with it.
걔랑 놀게 해주면 되잖아
있었네
게리랑 그 얘기 해봤니?
Did you talk to Gary
about moving in?
- 얘기했는데 같이 살아라
- 뭐?
I think you should do it.
He's a great guy and he loves you
a lot. You are a very lucky lady.
괜찮은 친구고 널 많이 사랑해
너 큰 횡재한 거야
You are useless!
이 쓸모 없는 화상아
Freaking out about commitment
is the one thing you can do...
할 줄 아는 게 그거밖에 없어서
맡겼더니 그걸 말아먹고 오니?
...and you can't even do that right!
Sorry. If he asked me,
I'd move in with him.
미안...
나라면 같이 살겠다
Get out of here, good-for-nothing.
저리 가라, 푼수야
Hey, Chandler.
- 안녕, 챈들러?
- 왔네
Hey, Gar.
Hey, sweetie.
자기야
Can I talk to you for a second?
- 잠깐 얘기 좀 할까?
- 그래
You look pretty today.
- 오늘 정말 예뻐
- 고마워, 알았어
Thanks. Okay.
Here's the thing.
- 다름이 아니라...
- 그래
I really want this relationship
to move forward.
난 우리 관계를 좀더
발전시켰으면 해
If you're not moving forward,
you're moving backwards.
진전이 없으면
후퇴하는 법이거든
그건 아니지
No, if you're not moving forward,
you're staying still.
진전이 없으면 가만있는 거야
가만있는 것도 좋아, 이걸 봐
And staying still is good.
Watch this.
- 피비?
- 왜?
I want you to move in with me.
나하고 같이 살자
That is so sweet.
그 말 정말 듣기 좋다
하지만 너무 이르지 않아?
우린 아직 서로를 잘 몰라
But don't you think
it's too soon?
There's so much we don't know
about each other.
Okay. I get it.
그래, 무슨 뜻인지 알겠어
충분한 준비도 없이 뛰어들고
싶진 않아, 이해하지?
I don't want us to jump into something
that we're not ready for.
I don't want
to mess up what we have.
지금 우리가 가진 것도 소중해
자칫 그것까지 망칠 수도 있잖아
I'm worried it's gonna
be a big mistake.
Which is why my answer is yes!
그래서 내 대답은 '네'야
Really?
정말?
You're so happy.
너무 좋아한다
Monica, stop throwing it so hard!
야, 살살 좀 던져
We're on the same team!
우린 다 같은 편이라고
You guys have been doing this
for four hours?
네 시간? 네 시간째
이러고들 있는 거야?
That's right, baby.
- 그렇단다
- 좋아, 나도 해
-All right. Let me in.
-No, no! Don't do it!
안 돼! 하지 마!
What?
뭐?
He's a dropper.
얘는 '떨굼쇠'야
Oh, yeah. That's right!
그래, 맞다!
I'm not a dropper!
누가 떨굼쇠야?
It's really a three-person
game, you know?
이건 원래 셋이 하는 게임이야
It's throwing and catching.
그냥 던지고 받는 거잖아
All right.
알았어
Oh, it's so hard.
얼씨구, 너무 어렵네
Don't worry, guys.
It's not a cat.
걱정 마, 고양이 아냐
Oh, good God!
이런, 세상에
이 요물을 어떡했으면 좋겠니?
I give up. I don't know what
I'm gonna do with this thing.
Baking it didn't help?
구워도 소용이 없드나?
산 데 가서 물러달라고 해
Take it back to where you got it.
I tried. They won't take her back.
그렇게는 해줄 수 없대
얘가 적그리스도의
앞잡이라서 그럴 거야
Maybe that's because she's
a minion of the Antichrist.
Why won't they take it?
왜 환불 못해준대?
현금은 곤란하고 동물로
바꿔가라는데 어떡해
They said they would only
give me store credit.
What am I gonna do?
Get 1000 regular cats?
보통 고양이 천 마리로 바꿔?
You said it was a show cat. Why don't you
show it, win some prize money.
쇼에 나가는 고양이라면
상금을 노려봐도 되겠네
참가비만 백 달러에다
Those shows cost a hundred bucks to enter,
and all you win are these ribbons...
상품으로 주는 리본도
다 망할 고양이 차지야
...which technically belong to the damn cat.
해결방법 찾을 때까지
당분간 우리 집에 두자
You can keep it until you
find out what to do with it.
지금 그게 문제니? 천 달러
날리고 성한 데 없이 긁히고
That's not the point.
I'm out $1000...
...I'm all scratched up...
이 민둥산 요물단지까지
떠맡게 된 상황에
...and I'm stuck with this stupid cat
that looks like a hand!
이런, 고양이 알레르기야
안 돼, 나한테 던지지 마!
Oh, my God!
The cat's made my eyes water.
Don't throw it to me!
눈이 침침하다니깐!
My vision's been compromised!
세상에, 됐어
그래...
Oh, God! Okay.
이제 괜찮아
큰일 날 뻔했네
It's okay. Man, that was close.
그래, 과민반응 문턱까지 갔지
Yeah, you almost overreacted
to something.
- 우리예요
- 어서 와요
중대발표가 있어요
-We have great news.
-We're moving in together. Yay!
우리 동거할 거다
잘됐지? 예!
Congratulations.
- 축하해
- 멋지다
- 그래, 너무 좋아
- 나두요
-I'm so excited!
-So am l.
You're not more excited than I am.
No way. I'm the most excited.
나보다 더 좋진 않을 걸
안 되지, 내가 제일 좋아
See you at the station later.
- 그럼 이따 서에서 봐
- 알았어
I'll see you later.
Don't forget about the moving-in!
- 같이 살기로 한 거 잊지 마
- 그래
So you're moving in with him?
같이 살기로 하다니
어떻게 된 거야?
거절할 수가 없었어
너무 상심하더라고
I couldn't tell him no. He got so sad.
Maybe it'll be all right.
괜찮을 거야
개리를 정말 좋아하니까
I do like him a lot...
...and probably do it
eventually, anyway.
결국은 그렇게 되지 않겠어?
Plus, think of all the money
I'll save on stamps.
우표 값도 많이 절약될 거고
Do you write him a lot?
그렇게 편지를 많이 쓰니?
I heard when people live together...
아니, 같이 살면 우표 값은
공동 부담한다던데, 아냐?
...they split the cost
of stamps, don't they?
- 그럼
- 맞아, 당연하지
-Yeah, yeah.
-That's right.
Sorry, the oven mitts
really freaked me out.
미안, 그 오븐장갑
진짜 무섭다
Hey, honey.
- 안녕?
- 어서 와
브루클린 하이츠에 괜찮은
아파트 있는지 알아봤어?
Did you find any apartments
in Brooklyn Heights?
아니, 없어
No, nothing.
-Oh, really?
-Yeah.
- 정말?
- 그래
-Nothing at all?
-No.
- 하나도 없어?
- 응, 빈집 나는 대로 들어가자
If something opens up, we'll move in.
If it has a pool. I need a pool.
근데 수영장은 꼭 있어야 돼
Can I talk to you?
피비, 얘기 좀 할까?
- 앉아
- 그래
Take a seat.
You okay?
괜찮아?
You feel all right?
기분 좋아?
당연히 기분 좋지
같이 살게 됐는데
I feel great, because
we're moving in together.
So you....
그러니까...
You checked the paper for listings
in Brooklyn Heights, right?
신문에서 브루클린 하이츠의
임대광고를 확인했다 이거지?
You checked the Post?
'포스트'지도 봤나?
Yeah, there was nothing.
그래, 한 군데도 없었어
- 물 좀 마셔도 돼?
- 조금 이따
-Can I get some water?
-ln a minute.
You checked today's Post?
- 오늘자 포스트도 봤어?
- 그래, 오늘자...
Yeah, today's.
이게 오늘자 포스트야
그리고 이건 내가 찾아낸 거지
Because this is today's Post.
And these are the listings I found.
Brooklyn Heights, two bedrooms.
Brooklyn Heights, one bedroom.
브루클린 하이츠, 침실 2개
브루클린 하이츠, 침실 1개
Brooklyn Heights, Brooklyn Heights,
Brooklyn Heights!
브루클린 하이츠, 브루클린
하이츠, 브루클린 하이츠!
Oh, are these for rent?
I thought people were just bragging.
그게 임대광고였어?
집 자랑한 건 줄 알았네
Let me tell you what's going on here.
내가 추리를 한번 해볼까?
Don't look at the table.
Look at me.
아니, 눈 깔지 말고 날 봐
Somebody asked someone
to move in with him.
어떤 사람이 누군가에게
동거를 제의했고
Someone said yes,
but now she has doubts...
누군가도 찬성했지만 지금은
그 결정에 확신이 없는 눈치야
...because things are moving too fast.
Does that sound possible?
가능성이 농후하지 않나?
그래, 맞아
그 누군가가 바로 나야
Yes, fine! I am someone!
You want me to say it?
I have doubts!
솔직히 자백할까?
난 확신이 없어
I'm sorry!
미안해
- 피비
- 왜?
It's okay that you feel this way.
그런 생각하는 것도 당연해
It is soon, and there's things
we don't know about each other.
빠른 건 사실이니까
서로에 대해 모르는 것도 많고
하지만 난 자기의 모든 면이 좋아
Everything I know about you,
I really like.
Things I don't know, I'll learn in
a place with our names on the mailbox.
모르는 부분은 우편함을 함께
쓰면서 차차 알아가고 싶어
That's so sweet.
너무 근사하다
자기야
But if it's too soon for you,
we don't have to do it.
하지만 자기가 부담스럽다면
굳이 같이 살 필요는 없어
I want you to be happy.
난 자기만 행복하면 돼
Living with you would make me happy.
- 자기랑 살면 행복할 거야
- 그렇게 말하지 않아도 돼
You don't have to say that.
I want to live with you.
I want to move in with you.
아니, 진심이야
같이 살고 싶어
Are you sure?
정말이야?
그래
당연하지, 좋아
Definitely, yes! Let's live in
an apartment we both live in.
- 우리 함께 사는 거야
- 잘 생각했어
Oh, that's great.
Oh, wait, one sec.
근데 잠깐만
거기, 거울 뒤의 당신!
뭘 쳐다보는 거야?
Hey, you! Behind the glass.
Who are you looking at?
I always wanted to say that every time
I was in these rooms, which was never.
여기 올 때마다 꼭 해보고
싶었어, 이번이 처음이지만
Show cat!
고양이 사세요
좋은 고양이 나왔어요
Quality show cat!
-Show cat!
-Oh, my God!
고양이 사세요
엄마야, 아기가 왜 이래요?
What's wrong with your baby?
아기가 아니라 고양이에요
That's not a baby. That's a cat.
-It's creepy-looking.
-Oh, no.
너무 징그럽네요
무슨 말씀이세요, 얼마나
착하고 귀여운데, 보세요
It's actually very sweet.
It's very sweet. Look.
Yeah. Do you want it?
어때요, 사실래요?
No, I hate cats.
난 고양이 싫어해요
Then what are you doing to me?
그럼 여기서 뭐하는 거죠?
가세요, 빨랑 비켜주세요
Get out of here, all right?
Move on!
돌겠네
What an unusual cat.
- 그 고양이 참 특이하다
- 네, 잘 보셨습니다
Yes, thank you! Exactly.
You want it?
- 맘에 드세요?
- 글쎄요
Maybe.
I was thinking about getting a cat
from the shelter, but....
안 그래도 하나 키울까 하고
보호소에 가볼 생각이었는데
-Okay. Why not?
-Oh, terrific! That'll be $2,000.
좋아요, 까짓 거 뭐
잘됐네요, 2천 달러예요
-What?
-Okay, 1000.
- 네?
- 좋아요, 천 달러
Didn't you want me to adopt your cat?
- 입양하는 건 줄 알았는데
- 그렇긴 하지만
I do, but you'll have to look at this
as more of an investment than a cat.
단순한 고양이로 보지 말고
투자라고 생각하세요
난 고양이만 있으면 돼요
Okay, yeah.
I just wanted a cat.
어허, 왜 이러실까...
Obviously, you know how to haggle,
so I won't try and take you on.
흥정을 할 줄 아시네
제가 손해 좀 보죠 뭐
8백 달러, 신고할지도 몰라요
장님 코 베어 가는 날강도니까
So $800, and I don't call the cops,
because you are robbing me blind!
Blind! Just take the cat.
Leave the money. Run away!
눈 감았다, 돈만 놔두고
얼른 고양이랑 튀세요
Run away. Damn it!
빨랑 튀어요
우라질!
Can't you at least smile or something?
넌 웃지도 못하니?
누가 방금 그 소리
못 들었어요?
Did anybody just hear that? Anybody?
-I'm starving.
-Come on, guys. Suck it up!
배고파 죽겠다
왜들 이럴까, 힘내
열 시간 채워야지
We're closing in on 10 hours.
It's gut-check time!
배포 확인 타임이야
I don't know who made you the boss.
We invented this game.
누구 맘대로 대장행세야
우리가 만들어낸 게임인데
왜 이래
지금처럼 만든 건 나야
I made this game what it is!
Not fun anymore?
요딴 식으로 재미없게?
I'm still hungry.
- 쓰러지겠다
- 집에 피자 남은 게 있는데
There's pizza at my place. We can eat
with one hand. Are you with me?
다들 한 손으로 먹을 수 있지?
따라올 거야?
-I am.
-All right, let's go! Come on!
- 좋아
- 그렇지, 가자!
Let's go, Team Monica!
따라들 오시라!
아싸, 모니카 팀!
We can work out the name later.
이름은 나중에 생각하자
레이첼, 네 고양이가
왜 여기 들어가 있지?
What is your cat doing in my bowl?
아냐, 통닭 녹이는 중이야
I'm defrosting a chicken.
I sold Mrs. Whiskerson.
- 참, 수염여사 팔아버렸어
- 이제 좀 살겠네
Thank God!
-Get your money back?
-Yeah, $1500.
- 돈은 받았어?
- 그래, 천 5백 달러
이윤까지 남겼어?
You made a profit?
I just came for the red velvet pillow.
- 빨간 벨벳 쿠션이 있다면서?
- 네
-There you go.
-Thanks, Rachel.
- 여기 있어요
- 고마워, 레이첼
Don't forget, you can come
visit her anytime.
얘 보고 싶으면 언제든지 와
Oh, good. Great.
I'll keep that in mind.
좋죠, 기억해둘게요
이봐
So is this some kind
of snake or something?
이거 무슨 뱀 종류인가?
I like waking up with you.
- 같이 일어나니까 정말 좋다
- 나도 너무 좋아
I like waking up with you too.
Oh, it's such a beautiful morning.
정말 아름다운 아침이야
I could stay here all day.
- 종일 여기 있어야겠다
- 그거 좋지
That would be great.
-We could have breakfast in bed.
-Wait, just a second.
- 침대에서 아침도 먹고...
- 잠깐만
에그머니!
Oh, no.
맙소사
All right. Come on, Monica!
Look alive. Come on!
아싸, 모니카
힘내는 거야
아싸, 힘내자
좋았어
- 로스
- 응?
Oh, I was having the best dream.
- 멋진 꿈을 꿨어
- 뭔데?
-What?
-I dreamed I was drowning...
내가 익사하는 꿈이었어
이 공 주고받는 게 아니라
...and not throwing this ball.
Oh, good. You're all up.
- 다들 깨어있었구나
- 어서 와
It's 6:00 in the morning.
Why aren't you at Gary's?
피비, 지금 아침 6시야
개리 집에 있을 시간 아냐?
- 다 끝났어
- 뭐?
Oh, yeah. That's over.
개리는 좋은 친구야
해결 못할 게 뭐 있어?
Gary's such a great guy.
You can work it out.
- 새를 쐈어
- 그럼 끝이네
-He shot a bird.
-That is over.
-I'm sorry.
-That's terrible.
- 어떡하니...
- 너무 심했다
Are you okay?
너 괜찮니?
I'll be all right.
그래, 괜찮아질 거야
Here, Phoebe.
이거 받아, 피비
I don't feel like playing.
놀고 싶은 기분 아냐
It's okay. It's okay.
괜찮아, 놀라지 마
It didn't happen.
No one needs to know.
없었던 걸로 하자
아무도 모르잖아
She's not an official ball player.
피비는 정규선수가 아냐
얘가 떨어뜨린 건 안 쳐줘
Only official ball players
can drop the ball.
-Come on.
-Let's go.
- 가자
- 그래
You wanna get breakfast?
- 피비, 너도 아침 먹을래?
- 그래
Okay, let's race!
좋아, 그럼 경주하자
먼저 가는 사람 1등, 하하!
First one there wins.
You guys wanna eat here?
- 여기서 먹을까?
- 그래, 좋아
정말 대단했지?
그 정도면 신기록 아냐?
That was great, huh?
Can you believe how long we threw it?
It is amazing it lasted that long.
진짜 오래갔다
그러게, 팔 떨어지겠다
My arm is killing me.
No, I meant with
the dropper over here.
아니, 저 떨굼쇠 말이야
How did I get this
reputation as a dropper?
내가 어쩌다 떨굼쇠가 됐지?
다른 건 몰라도
떨굼쇠는 절대 아냐
I am anything but a dropper.
Ross!
로스